Mosarimi 15

Reykjavik, Postal Code: 112, Iceland

897-8301

heimdal.is

antonheimdal@protonmail.com

github.com/aheimdal

Anton H. Heimdal

Goals

I want to earn experience and accumulate skills in the computer programming industry to work towards financial freedom to have a better live set up for me and my son. To further my skill set I will use Udemy and other online platforms to improve my knowledge in the field of programming and designing.



EXPERIENCE

Smakranar ehf, Reykjavik - Crane Operator

May 2017 - PRESENT

• I have licenses to operate small cranes and drive trucks with trailers.

Window Cleaning Contractor, Reykjavik — Contractor Window Cleaner July 2019 - PRESENT

• Extra job to pay the bills to be able to stay in school.

Malbikunarstodin Colas ehf, Hafnarfjordur - Group leader

July 2017 - August 2017

- Worked as a group supervisor
- As a truck driver as well as machine operator

EDUCATION

University of Iceland, Reykjavik - Bachelor's Degree

August 2017 - February 2021 (Graduating)

University of Reykjavik, Reykjavik - Students Degree

August 2014 - December 2015

Finished a Students degree equivalent in 3 semesters

Extra Courses taken outside of school

Got my truck and machine licence in a Driving Educational school called New Driving school (Nýji Ökuskólinn)

Languages

I speak Icelandic (Native language), English fluently, German (Basic), Danish (Basic) and Norwegian (Basic).

Computer Knowledge

I have good knowledge on operating systems like windows and Linux and I have good grasp on C#, Python, Java, Javascript, ATOM, Angular, Node.js JSON. All this knowledge has been accumulated through my school work at the University of Tceland.

In my spare time I have been learning on the Unity engine with the help of Udemy courses.

I also have a good understanding on how Github works and how to use it in projects.

Personal Projects

I have personalized website heimdal.is where I have a list of my finished projects where a link to the source code is available and in some cases live version of the project.

Run Gun Renegade - Group project done by 4 members for the Course "COMPUTER GAME PROGRAMMING" - (TÖL308G - FALL 2018)

RVK - A group project with 4 members where we build a software for web and mobile use where a user could find several locations depending on his wishes within Reykjavik, Iceland. "SOFTWARE PROJECT 1" - (HBV501G - FALL 2019)

Recommendations

Erlingur Snær Erlingsson +354 699 4241 (Smakranar ehf, Manager)